<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<atom:link href="https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<title>hhhhhhhhhn</title>
	<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings</link>
	<description>hhhhhhhhhn's writings</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 23:02:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-us</language>

		<item>
			<title>A Reflection on Vim-like Text Editors</title>
			<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/a-reflection-on-vim-like-text-editors.html</link>
			<guid>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/a-reflection-on-vim-like-text-editors.html</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>
As a programmer, choosing the right text editor is crucial
since you may spend several hours a day working in it.
With so many options available,
Vim-like text editors have gained a special reputation among enthusiasts.
In this reflection,
I would like to consider how these editors hold up to scrutiny
and whether they still deserve their high status...</description>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Rust is Nice</title>
			<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/rust-is-nice.html</link>
			<guid>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/rust-is-nice.html</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 21:58:24 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>
After putting it off for years,
I finally learned Rust.
Even though it has been the most loved programming language since 2016,
I still could not get over the complex-appearing syntax.
Luckily, I was planning on making a program in C and had a lot of free time,
so I decided to do it in a new programming language.
After quickly considering APL,
I noticed that it was probably the time to learn Rust.
Now I understand why people like it...</description>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Markdown: A Patch for the Modern Web</title>
			<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/markdown--a-patch-for-the-modern-web.html</link>
			<guid>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/markdown--a-patch-for-the-modern-web.html</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 02:08:44 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>
I think it is no secret that websites have become worse with time.
From ads to pop-ups to terrible load times,
it seems that looking stuff up gets harder as every second goes by.
People have tried to reform the Internet.
Projects like Gopher1
and Gemini come to mind.
Although they have been very successful in their niches (including me),
I find it hard to believe regular people are using them.
I think the solution is often overlooked in between attempts to reinvent the wheel.
It is a format that is already widely used: Markdown...</description>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Approximating 𝑒 in 6½ Programming Languages</title>
			<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/approximating----in-6--programming-languages.html</link>
			<guid>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/approximating----in-6--programming-languages.html</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 21:45:23 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>
I often use programming languages to play around with mathematical problems,
as they are often the fastest option to quickly iterate over ideas.
I have used the usual scripting options, like Python, JavaScript, Julia, Go, and even bc.
That left me wanting to compare some of them,
but then I noticed I could use the opportunity to compare a more diverse range of languages.
This is the result of the comparison...</description>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Testing 3 Common Shell Optimizations</title>
			<link>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/testing-3-common-shell-optimizations.html</link>
			<guid>https://hhhhhhhhhn.com/writings/testing-3-common-shell-optimizations.html</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 13:48:44 GMT</pubDate>
			<description>
Although worrying about performance in shell scripts seems oxymoronic at first (at least to me),
I have seen enough tips to become curious about the actual benefits of some of them.
So, I decided to put three common ones to the test, with a few self-made benchmarks...</description>
		</item>

</channel>
</rss>
